I saw the static in your eyes, the silent
screams, the practiced lies.
A pain, a smile, a hollow shell Trapped inside a
private hell I tried cold, I tried to warn All
that cold and broken morn You couldn't hear my
quiet plea But you are finally back with me
And I will never let you go again This is a promise
not a warning for when If the darkness ever calls
your name I'll be the fire, I'll be the flame And
if I have to
With my own two hands
I'll drag you back from those broken lands I'll
take
I'll be the flute song in your head for every
single word unsaid
A steady note, a gentle sound on this new and
solid ground
No more silence, no more fear As long as I am
standing here You'll never have to walk alone
I'll bring my broken brother home
I will never let you go again This is a promise,
not a word if or when If the darkness ever calls
your name I'll be the fire, I'll be the flame And
if I have to With my own two hands,
I'll drag you back from those broken lands.